http://www.ucumiami.org/en/privacy-policy

empty text
empty text
skip to main content
HomeProducts & ServicesBusiness ServicesCheckingCurrent RatesSavings and CD RatesLoan RateseServicesInvestments/InsuranceLoansMastercard Credit CardsRewards MastercardOther ServicesRelationship RewardsSavingsOnline ServicesNew e*branch and Bill Payer Has Arrived!e*branch Online Accesse*branch LoginMobile e*branchEquifax Credit WatchReorder ChecksMastercard AlertsVISA Purchase AlertsAbout UsMembershipUniversity of MiamiFlorida International University St. Thomas UniversityThe Legal CommunityThe Miami-Dade CommunityContact UsATM SitesCareersHoliday ClosingsLocate UsEducationALERTS!EMV SmartCardsHow to Avoid Fraud! ID Theft PreventionLatest News Mastercard Lost/Stolen/DisputesMastercard AlertsCredit Reports and ScoresProtect YourselfVisa Debit Lost/Stolen/Disputes Phishing Vishing and SmishingVISA Purchase AlertsCash Hash - Financial EducationATMs
HomeProducts & ServicesBusiness ServicesCheckingCurrent RatesSavings and CD RatesLoan RateseServicesInvestments/InsuranceLoansMastercard Credit CardsRewards MastercardOther ServicesRelationship RewardsSavingsOnline ServicesNew e*branch and Bill Payer Has Arrived!e*branch Online Accesse*branch LoginMobile e*branchEquifax Credit WatchReorder ChecksMastercard AlertsVISA Purchase AlertsAbout UsMembershipUniversity of MiamiFlorida International University St. Thomas UniversityThe Legal CommunityThe Miami-Dade CommunityContact UsATM SitesCareersHoliday ClosingsLocate UsEducationALERTS!EMV SmartCardsHow to Avoid Fraud! ID Theft PreventionLatest News Mastercard Lost/Stolen/DisputesMastercard AlertsCredit Reports and ScoresProtect YourselfVisa Debit Lost/Stolen/Disputes Phishing Vishing and SmishingVISA Purchase AlertsCash Hash - Financial EducationATMs
Privacy Notice
font size
decrease font size
increase font size
At University Credit Union, your privacy is a top priority. This notice describes how we protect the privacy of your personal information. Throughout this notice, the word "information" refers to personal information about you that may not be publicly available.
FACTS
WHAT DOES UNIVERSITY CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all of the sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
• Social Security Number and Account Transactions  • Account Balances and Credit Scores  • Payment History and Credit History
How?
All financial companies need to share member’s personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list reasons financial companies can share their member’s personal information; the reasons University Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your information
Does University CU share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
YES
NO
For our marketing purposes - to offer our product and services to you
YES
NO
For joint marketing with other financial companies
YES
NO
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
NO
We don't share information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
NO
We don't share information about your transactions and experiences
For non-affiliates to market to you
YES
YES
To limit our sharing
Call our Call Center Department at (786) 425-5000 or (800) 230-4832, (Monday - Friday, 8:00 am - 5:00 pm)
Please Note: If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?
(786) 425-5000 or (800) 230-4832
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
University Credit Union
What we do
How does University Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings
University Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you  • open an account or apply for a loan  • make deposits or withdrawals  • show your government issues ID
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only  • sharing for affiliates everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness  • affiliates from using your information to market to you  • sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choice will apply to everyone on your account.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
• University Credit Union has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.    • Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
• Our joint markieting partners include insurance companies
back to top
APPLY FOR A LOAN
Products & Services
Business Services Checking Credit Cards Investments/Insurance Loans Other Services Relationship Rewards Savings Auto Advisors
Online Services
New e*branch and Mobile e*branch e*branch Online Login eServices Equifax Credit Watch Mastercard Alerts Reorder Checks Visa Purchase Alerts Social Media Statement
Membership
University of Miami Florida International University St. Thomas University The Legal Community The Miami-Dade Community
About Us
About UsATM SitesCareersContact UsCurrent Fee Schedule Holiday ClosingsLocate Us
Protection
EMV SmartCards ID Theft Protection Lost/Stolen Mastercard Lost/Stolen Visa Debit Mastercard Alerts Protect Yourself VISA Purchase Alerts
News & Alerts
ALERTS! Consumer Protection AwarenessHow to Avoid Fraud! Security Alert - Advance Fee Loan ScamsAlert - Romance Scams: Recognition and Recovery
Routing And Transit Number: 267077850
This credit union is federally insured by the National Credit Union Administration. Your savings federally insured to at least $250,000 and backed by the full faith and credit of the United States Government.  National Credit Union Administration, a U.S. Government Agency.  Rates are current as of June 2019 unless otherwise noted and are subject to change.
APY = Annual Percentage Yield
APR = Annual Percentage Rate
